hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Sand Coffin!
I'll do it.
No! Please back me up.
I got sand in my mouth...
P-Please let me go!
You wouldn't be able to do
anything in your current state...
I'll do it.
Please be careful!
That guy attacks with bones!
Like earlier...
he does things like shoot bones
and extrude bones from inside his body...
He controls bones freely!
Gaara of the Desert...
You use sand
as the name implies, huh...?
Showdown
of
the
Strongest!
Gaara vs Kimimaro!!
Tough defense using sand...
He... isn't a close-range combat type...
Getting close would be difficult, huh.
It's coming!
Digital Shrapnel!
There's no waste in his movements...
Sure enough,
he's a considerable Taijutsu user.
Attack and defense are one...
He attacks and defends
with sand, huh?
However, the amount of sand
he can control is probably...
...about the amount of sand
inside the gourd.
Gaara of the Desert...
A dopey nickname.
You can't do anything
if you don't have sand.
Going to the trouble of walking around
carrying heavy sand
is the very proof of that.
Sand Shower...
How trite...
As long as I have sand
I can do anything.
You're the one who's dopey...
It's easy for me to do things
like create sand with dirt...
I get it...
With his own sand he grinds things
like rocks and minerals in dirt
and makes it into sand.
So he was sending his own sand
beneath the ground
and adding new sand, huh...?
Gaara of the Desert...
His nickname isn't just for display.
Excellent!
You did it!
Not yet.
Sand Burial!
I'm reminded of that man
when I look at that guy.
Huh?
Uchiha Sasuke!
He had the same eyes
as that guy...
The same eyes?
Wanting to verify the value
of one's own existence...
Such eyes...
Sasuke!
Sasuke.
You're here, aren't you?!
At least answer me!
What's gotten into you?!
I don't hate the darkness...
The darkness is where
I was brought up...
Why am I... in a place like this?
Did I do something wrong?
Is there really God...?
If there is, why confine me
in a place like this?
Who's there?
It doesn't matter who I am...
Get out!
Kimimaro, the time has come to use you...
Huh?
For our sake,
for the Kaguya Clan...
Fight!
Yes... To fight.
That is...
the only thing I can do now.
N-No way...
That's quite some pressure...
I would've been flattened
just like that
had I not made a membrane
of bone just below the skin.
Bones... That guy's a monster too.
It's a troublesome body, isn't it?
I underestimated you...
But I won't be caught by
your sand anymore.
Sand Tsunami!
Wow... It's beyond
the scope of
escaping from the sand
or not getting caught...
To think it would change
the terrain itself...
You... You did it.
Not yet.
Giant Sand Burial!
H-He's so strong...
He's gotten even stronger
than when he fought me.
But... this time for sure...
He's a persistent guy...
Huh?!
I'm still... alive...
Then... There's still significance
for me to live.
From now we're going
to launch a night attack
on the Hidden Mist Village...
As they are disconcerted
from that incident
now is the perfect time for us
to make them realize our ferocity!
Make them realize the ferocity
of the Kaguya Clan!
— Yeah!
— Right!
What're you doing, Kimimaro?
Get going!
I don't know what to do...
You don't need to think
deeply about it.
Go down to the Hidden Mist Village
and kill every last person
you encounter!
Just act on your instincts!
Are you of the Hidden Mist Village?
No...
I-I see... Excuse me!
Haku?
Oh... no. It's nothing, Zabuza-san.
We don't have time to be stopping.
Let's hurry!
Right!
He had the same eyes as I...
Before I met Zabuza-san...
Hold it!
You're a hasty one, aren't you?
I'm not from this village.
The thing you are after is right there...
Now go.
It seems to have begun...
The Kaguya Clan...
Fools who can only find
their own path of life by fighting...
It was long ago
when a simple-minded group that
just enjoyed slaughtering was acceptable.
With a governed organization
as an opponent
they just become fools
rushing towards death
if they fight only with power...
Are we the only survivors...?
It seems we're surrounded...
The defense was tighter
than we thought.
We have no choice...
Now it's come to this,
take along with you
every person you can!
We'll have them entertain us
as much as possible!
What do I fight for...?
What am I...?
Without knowing anything
I just kept on fighting.
The time has come to use you...
I'm needed...
That was the only thing
that got my body moving.
And...
I was also able to figure out that...
I couldn't live if I didn't fight.
Dawn broke...
And I learned that...
I myself was the only one
to survive.
Again, I'm all alone...
By myself I just wandered
aimlessly from place to place.
This is...
The flower from back then...?
Why are you blooming
in a place like this?
Why won't you answer?
You're ignoring me too, huh?!
There's no way you'd be seen
by someone in a place like this yet you...!
That's enough...
Maybe... there's no significance to living.
But you might be able to
discover something interesting
by continuing to live... right?
Like how you discovered that flower...
Like how I discovered you.
Okay, let's go...
Back then...
Orochimaru-sama said that but...
People are born with
some kind of significance.
That's what I think...
some kind of important mission.
The mission for me...
is to protect Orochimaru-sama
and his ambition.
What's... that?!
Come back, Sasuke!
Everyone's worried about you!
Damn it...
It's so dark I can't see anything!
You've got better eyes than me.
Sasuke is in the darkness now...
N-Neji?!
You'll be unable to catch up
with Sasuke
if you stop in a place like this...
Neji!
Yeah... You're right!
This isn't the time to stop.
Just wait! I'll take Sasuke
back home no matter what!
Sasuke!
Sand Coffin!
That form...?!
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
I'm saved. That's excellent.
To think you could do such a thing!
He was persistent
but this is the end...
He'll never come out again.
Brainwashed by Orochimaru...
It's not brainwashing!
That person understands me!
What do you guys know?!
Next time:
"An Implacable Punch! Dance of the Seedling Fern."